

MARY JOY C. BONGCO Saint Jude, Villalimpia, Loay, 6303 Bohol +63 (0) 9284312709

bongcomary@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

To seek an opportunity where I can acquire knowledge and skills that will expand the potential I have acquired during my computer engineering studies and obtain chances by being able to orientate myself better. I hope to acquire new, specialized skills necessary for career mobility and growth.

PERSONAL BACKGROUND

AGE : 30 years old

DATE OF BIRTH : October 20, 1993

CITIZENSHIP : Filipino

CIVIL STATUS : Single (engaged with 2 children)

RELIGION : Roman Catholic

PARENTS : Asteria Caga-anan Bongco & Euberto Dango Bongco

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

COLLEGE

UNIVERSITY OF BOHOL

in Maria Clara Street, Tagbilaran City, Bohol

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

SY: 2012 – Present (incl. 7 years break)

SECONDARY

ALBURQUERQUE NATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL

HOLY TRINITY ACADEMY

in Tagbilaran East Rd, Alburquerque, Bohol

in Loay Interior Road, Loay, Bohol

SY: 2008 - 2010

SY: 2006 - 2007

ELEMENTARY

VILLALIMPIA ELEMENTARY SCHOOL

in Villalimpia, Loay, Bohol SY: 2000 - 2006

SEMINARS & CERTIFICATIONS

December 2023 | Seminar on 3D printing of EAGLE files, on Enhancing Software

Development Skills and on Robotics at University of Bohol in Tagbilaran City

Speakers: Rumil Christian Seloveres and Benjie Juabot BSCOMPE III

October 2023 Top 25 Regional Finalists in the 8th Annual Philippine Startup Challenge

18th place with "Cradle Talk"

at Department of Information and Communications Technology (DICT)

Central Visayas Regional Office in Cebu City

October 2023 Webinar on Quantum Computing Lecture Series and Hackathon

Speaker: DICT

October 2023 **Bohol i2i Idea to Innovation**

Introducing innovative COMPE and ECE products, "Cradle Talk"

at Panda Tea Garden Suites, Tagbilaran City

September 2023 **Seminar on PhilNITS Certification Exams**

at Holy Name University in Tagbilaran City

Speaker: Information Technology Professional Examination Council

(ITPEC)

August 2023 Cyber Security Webinar

Speaker: DICT

April 2023 ICT Student Congress 2023

at University of Bohol in Tagbilaran City

Speaker: Philippine Society of Information Technology Educators (PSiTE)

January 2023 Emergency First Aid Training

at UB Instructional Resource Center

December 2022 Conducted a conference for Printed Circuit Board (PCB) Designing

to Computer Engineering and Electrical Engineering students

COMPUTER SKILLS

Hardware Designing - Printed Circuit Board (PCB) designing

- Logic circuit designing

Robotics circuit designing

- Simulation circuit designing

Graphic design tools: Canva, Picsart

- CAD tools: AutoCAD, Easily Applicable Graphical Layout Editor

(EAGLE)

Programming - C# programming

(soft-skills) - React.js web programming

HTML web programming, encoding

Others - Befunky photo editor

- Microsoft 365 (PowerPoint, Excel, Word, Outlook)

WORK EXPERIENCE

2013 – 2015 Wedding Staff Coordinator at Jazz DUO Wedding Planner

(job alongside my studies, on call service)

 Serve as a personal assistant of the bride. Assists all her needs from make-up session, photo shoots, wedding itself until reception

2010 - 2012 Sales Clerk at City Square Mall Tagbilaran City

- Assist customers in finding the products they are looking for.
- Answer customer inquiries and provide information on products, returns and store policies.
- Keep track of stock levels, order and receive new inventory to ensure that products are always available for customers.

LANGUAGE

- Cebuano (mother tongue)
- Tagalog / Filipino (fluent)
- English (fluent)

ETHICS

- Equality of respect and opportunity
- Dedication and determination
- Capable to work in team and flexible

REFERENCES

Engr. Liduvina Namocatcat

Instructor

Email: <u>llnamocatcat@gmail.com</u>, Mob.: +63 (0) 995 907 6922

Engr. Victor John Anunciado

Intructor

Email: vilanunciado@universityofbohol.edu.ph, Mob.: +63 (0) 945 480 9029

Mr. Jaime Cinchez

Brgy. Kagawad and Operation Manager of St Vincent Driving School

Email: <u>jaimecinchez2@gmail.com</u>, Mob.: +63 (0) 950 817 3910

I hereby certify that the above-mentioned information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.